So, let's start from where we left off, which is,
我们从刚刚停下的地方继续
we have a complicated network architecture which would be
我们有一个复杂的网络架构
more complicated than we need but we need to live with it.
比我们所需的要复杂 但是我们需要采用这一架构
So, let's look at the process of training.
我们看看训练流程
We start with random weights in her first epoch and we get a model like this one,
我们在第一个 epoch 中以随机权重开始 获得这样的模型
which makes lots of mistakes.
有很多错误
Now as we train, let's say for 20 epochs we get a pretty good model.
假设训练 20 个 epoch 后 我们获得了很好的模型
But then, let's say we keep going for a 100 epochs,
但是假设继续 100 个 epoch
we'll get something that fits the data much better,
我们将获得数据拟合效果更好的模型
but we can see that this is starting to over-fit.
但是我们看到有点过拟合了
If we go for even more,
假设我们再训练 600 个 epoch
say 600 epochs, then the model heavily over-fits.
模型变得严重过拟合
We can see that the blue region is pretty much a bunch of circles around the blue points.
可以看到蓝色区域差不多就是一堆围绕蓝点的圆圈
This fits the training data really well,
这样对训练数据拟合的很好
but it will generalize horribly.
但是无法泛化
Imagine a new blue point in the blue area.
假设蓝色区域有个新的蓝点
This point will most likely be classified as red unless it's super close to a blue point.
这个点很有可能会被分类为红色 除非它离某个蓝点非常近
So, let's try to evaluate these models by adding a testing set such as these points.
我们尝试添加一些测试集来评估这些模型 例如添加这些点
Let's make a plot of the error in the training set
我们将训练集和测试集相对于
and the testing set with respect to each epoch.
每个 epoch 的误差绘制成图表
For the first epoch,
对于第一个 epoch
since the model is completely random,
因为模型完全是随机的
then it badly misclassifies both the training and the testing sets.
那么对训练集和测试集的分类都很糟糕
So, both the training error and the testing error are large.
所以训练误差和测试误差都很大
We can plot them over here.
我们将其画到这里
For the 20 epoch,
对于第 20 个 epoch
we have a much better model which fit the training data pretty well,
模型好多了 能够很好地拟合训练数据
and it also does well in the testing set.
测试集也能很好地拟合
So, both errors are relatively small and we'll plot them over here.
所以两个误差都相对比较小 画在这里
For the 100 epoch,
对于第 100 个 epoch
we see that we're starting to over-fit.
我们看到我们开始过拟合了
The model fits the data very well but it starts making mistakes in the testing data.
模型能很好地拟合数据 但是开始在测试数据中出错了
We realize that the training error keeps decreasing,
我们看到训练误差不断下降
but the testing error starts increasing,
但是测试误差开始升高了
so, we plot them over here.
将它们画到这里
Now, for the 600 epoch, we're badly over-fitting.
对于第 600 个 epoch 我们严重过拟合了
We can see that the training error is very tiny because the data fits the training set
可以看到训练误差非常小 因为数据可以非常完美地拟合训练集
really well but the model makes tons of mistakes in the testing data.
但是模型在测试集中犯了大量错误
So, the testing error is large.
所以测试误差很大
We plot them over here.
将它们画到这里
Now, we draw the curves that connect the training and testing errors.
现在画出连接训练误差和测试误差的曲线
So, in this plot,
在此图中
it is quite clear when we stop under-fitting and start over-fitting,
很清楚何时停止欠拟合并开始过拟合
the training curve is always decreasing since as we train the model,
训练曲线始终会下降 因为在我们训练模型时
we keep fitting the training data better and better.
我们不断越来越好地拟合数据
The testing error is large when we're under-fitting because the model is not exact.
当我们欠拟合时 测试误差很大 因为模型不够精确
Then it decreases as the model generalizes well until it gets
随着模型开始很好地泛化 它不断降低
to a minimum point - the Goldilocks spot.
直到抵达最低点（黄金点）
And finally, once we pass that spot,
最终 当我们超过该点后
the model starts over-fitting again since it stops
模型开始过拟合
generalizing and just starts memorizing the training data.
因为它已无法泛化并开始记住训练数据
This plot is called the model complexity graph.
这个图表叫做模型复杂度图表
In the Y-axis, we have a measure of
在 y 轴上是误差测量结果
the error and in the X-axis we have a measure of the complexity of the model.
在 x 轴上是模型复杂度测量结果
In this case, it's the number of epochs.
这里是 epoch 数量
And as you can see,
可以看出
in the left we have high testing and training error, so we're under-fitting.
在左侧是很高的测试和训练误差 所以我们欠拟合
In the right, we have a high testing error and low training error, so we're over-fitting.
在右侧有很高的测试误差和很低的训练误差 所以我们过拟合
And somewhere in the middle,
在中间
we have our happy Goldilocks point.
是令人满意的黄金点
So, this determines the number of epochs we'll be using.
这个就决定了我们要使用的 epoch 次数
So, in summary, what we do is,
总结下
we degrade in descent until the testing error stops decreasing and starts to increase.
我们要做的是降低梯度 直到测试误差停止降低并开始增大
At that moment, we stop.
这时候 我们就停止
This algorithm is called Early Stopping and is widely used to train neural networks.
这个算法叫做早期停止法 广泛用于训练神经网络